<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jack Bubala&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://jackbubala.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jack Bubala&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jackbubala.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We Want...UCF?</title>
      <link>http://jackbubala.github.io/2021/04/25/we-want-ucf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jackbubala.github.io/2021/04/25/we-want-ucf/</guid>
      <description>We want Bama! That has been the call of underdog teams for years, ever since Nick Saban took over the Alabama Crimson Tide football team and made them into the the powerhouse they are today. Watch any episode of College Gameday from the past few years and you’re bound to see someone holding a sign claiming the school hosting Gameday could hang with the roll with the Tide. However, this isn’t about Alabama this is about the teams who haven’t been able to find success and the underdog who never got their chance to show the world just how good they were on college football’s biggest stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Bears Are Now On The Clock</title>
      <link>http://jackbubala.github.io/2021/04/04/the-chicago-bears-are-now-on-the-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jackbubala.github.io/2021/04/04/the-chicago-bears-are-now-on-the-clock/</guid>
      <description>After a mediocre at best 8-8 season, the Chicago Bears let their once thought to be franchise quarterback, Mitchell Trubisky, walk and become a free agent. A move expected by many brought a wave of excitement as rumors of Russell Wilson started swirling, leading Bears fans to believe that they may finally have found their guy. Instead, Wilson is staying in Seattle and Andy Dalton is coming to Chicago after leading an above-average Cowboys team to a below-average season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
